//Questions and options are sourced from https://www.ultimatequizquestions.com/vegetable-quiz-questions/
//Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers

let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: 'Which animal does Lisie would most likely pet?',
        answer: "Dog",
        options: [
            "Cat",
            "Gold fish",
            "Turtle",
            "Dog"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: 'What type of movies does Lisie like?',
        answer: "Romance",
        options: [
            "Action",
            "Romance",
            "Comedy",
            "Horror"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: 'In Lisie\'s free time, what she would do?',
        answer: "Read and watch new to dos on youtube",
        options: [
            "Read and watch new to dos on youtube",
            "Go to the beach",
            "Haging out with friends",
            "Watch a new movie"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: 'Lisie and I ',
        answer: "All of the above",
        options: [
            "were both baptized in August",
            "Went to UCF",
            "All of the above",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: 'What is one thing I learned from her?',
        answer: "Be Patient",
        options: [
            "Be a Servant of God",
            "Dreans come true",
            "Be Patient",
            "Be Motivated"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: 'How many ministry i oversee at church?',
        answer: "2",
        options: [
            "0",
            "1",
            "2",
            "3"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: 'What is my fav color?',
        answer: "Red",
        options: [
            "Red",
            "Green",
            "BLue",
            "Yellow"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: 'Which city i am from?',
        answer: "Cayes",
        options: [
            "Cayes",
            "Aquin",
            "Jeremy",
            "Jacmel"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: 'What was the first time I messaged Lise? Dont look in your IG timeline loll',
        answer: "February 11",
        options: [
            "February 11",
            "May 11",
            "January 11",
            "February 14"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: 'What is your favorite color?',
        answer: "Pink",
        options: [
            "Blue",
            "Red",
            "Pink",
            "turquoise"
        ]
    },
]

